gadgetwide.com 2015-04-18

# Privacy Policy | GadgetWide Solutions

## Privacy Terms and Conditions

GadgetWide (VBD S.P) is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those individuals using this website, our online facilities and all associated services accurate, confidential, secure and private.

### **GadgetWide Terms of Use**

Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to **exceed** most existing **privacy** **standards**.

THEREFORE, this privacy policy shall apply to GadgetWide and all associated content, and thus it shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. **Through the use** of GadgetWide’s services **you are** herein **consenting** to the **following** data **procedures** expressed within this agreement.

#### **Collection of information**

Our **software**  applications **collect** various types of **information** , such as:

  * Mandatory information which includes your name, address, e-mail address, ( **voluntary** ) billing and/or credit card information etc., which is used when making use of our website application services or when voluntarily selected may be used when you purchase products and/or services and to deliver the services you have requested

  * **Information** that is **collected** when **using** GadgetWide’s **website** is completely **inputted** **by** the **user**. Information is **NEVER**   **automatically collected** when visiting our website, third party tracking cookies or anything of that nature.

**GadgetWide  only** **collects** personal **information** that **you knowingly** and willingly **provide** by way of registration. It is the intent of GadgetWide to use your personal information only for the purpose of which it was requested and any additional uses specifically provided on this website.

GadgetWide may have the occasion to collect anonymous demographic information, such as age, gender, and region at a later time. We may also gather information about the type of mobile device you are using, IMEI number, serial number or type of operating system to assist us in providing and maintaining superior quality service.

 It is **highly recommended** and suggested that you **review** the **privacy policies** and statements of any organization you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in which other establishments garner, make use of and share information collected.

#### **Use of Information Collected**

GadgetWide may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website/services and associated sites and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request.

At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from GadgetWide’s website/services and associated sites.

GadgetWide  **WILL NEVER** **contact you** with **regards** to completing **surveys** and/or **research** questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered by us or any other organization.

**GadgetWide does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of our customer lists and/or names to any third parties.**

 GadgetWide may deem it necessary to follow registration statistics, websites and/or pages that our users may frequent only within the GadgetWide eco-system in an effort to gleam what types of services and/or products may be the most popular to customers or the general public.

**GadgetWide may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:**

  * **  Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process that may be served upon GadgetWide and/or our website/services and associated sites;**

  * **  Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of GadgetWide; and**

  * **  Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of GadgetWide’s website/services and associated sites and/or its proprietors and the general public.**

#### **Children Under Age of 13**

GadgetWide does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use our website/services and associated sites.

#### **Unsubscribe or Opt-Out**

Although GadgetWide will not involuntarily send users any form of promotional material it is important to state that all users and/or visitors using our website/services and associated sites have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to our website/services and associated sites please send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to unsubscribe@gadgetwide.com. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third party websites, you must go to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or opt-out.

#### **The Internet and Links to Other Web Sites**

Our website does contain links to affiliate and other websites. GadgetWide does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our website application and associated website.

#### **Security**

> YOU SHOULD KNOW THIS

**When users leave comments on articles or  posts, unique network identifiers are collected and posted alongside each publicly posted comment. The information includes but is not limited to, IP address, MAC address, Operating System (OS), web browser, version indicators and more. This data is collected and re-posted in order to minimize SPAM and threatening articles of data. The collected information from user comments also serve as unique identifiers assisting us in targeting users, sorting through comments and more. The justification of these practices would likely be used in an example scenario such as, obtaining the name of a comments author (in order to identify a cingular user enrolled in a comment-based give-away or other similar situation). This type of data usage is the most commonly used form such as that stated within the last example.      **

GadgetWide shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user’s personal information under our control.

When a user chooses to purchase products and/or services GadgetWide uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) for billing and/or credit card information used for authentication and private communications in an effort to build users’ trust and confidence in GadgetWide by providing simple and secure access and communication of credit card and personal information.

#### **Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement**

GadgetWide reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those changes via website update and our website homepage at www.gadgetwide.com, so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time GadgetWide decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email or other media. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate manner.

#### **Acceptance of Terms**

Through the use of this website/service, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our website/services and associated sites. In addition, your continued use of our website/services and associated sites following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.

#### **Data Removal Practices**

GadgetWide strongly believes in maintaining the privacy and rights of our users, with that we practice routine deletion of any content collected via our site and or services. We **prefer** to **keep** you, **OUR USERS** information **anonymous** unless otherwise specifically notified.

#### **Concerns  about your Privacy **

If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website/services and associated sites, contact us at the following email, telephone number.

* * *

## ****

#### **GadgetWide Solutions**

**Email:**  [support@gadgetwide.com](mailto:support@gadgetwide.com)  
**Telephone Number:**  [818-495-5758](call:818-495-5758)

* * *

#### **_Varastad B. DerBedrosian Sole Proprietor_**

GadgetWide is fully operated and a wholly owned subsidiary of  Varastad B. DerBedrosian Sole Proprietorship | VBD S.P |

The brands or names Varastad, GadgetWide, VBD S.P and others are typically referenced and commonly used on this website\services utilizing aliases as identifiers to label the parent entity or founder of GadgetWide. Some of  the names used are Varo DerBedrosian, Varo, GW, Us, We, Our and others not specifically mentioned

**Address:  **GadgetWide | VBD S.P | Glendale | California | United States

**Web Address:  **http://www.gadgetwide.com

#### **Concerned About Your Privacy? | Contact Us**
